<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Apple Hot News</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/hotnews/</link>
<description>Hot News provided by Apple.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Copyright 2010, Apple Inc.</copyright>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2010 11:28:51 PDT</pubDate>
<lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2010 11:28:51 PDT</lastBuildDate>
<category>Apple</category>
<generator>In house</generator>
<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss/</docs><item>
<title>iPhone Again Tops Smartphone Satisfaction Survey</title>
<link>http://news.cnet.com/8301-13579_3-20017417-37.html</link>
<description>CNET reports that for the fourth consecutive year, J.D. Power and Associates has ranked Apple highest in customer satisfaction among smartphone manufacturers. The study showed that iPhone scored particularly well in ease of operation, operating system, features, and physical design.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 17:03:25 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Discovering Ancient Pompeii with iPad</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/ipad/pompeii/</link>
<description>Archaeologist Steven Ellis and his team are using iPad — with apps like Pages, FMTouch, iDraw, OmniGraffle, and Photos — to capture invaluable historical data in the trenches at Pompeii. Says Ellis, “That my team could both type and draw on the screen, and also examine all previously entered data, made it an ideal single-device solution.”</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2010 09:31:00 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>iPad Tops Consumer Satisfaction Survey</title>
<link>http://www.cnbc.com/id/39290945/</link>
<description>CNBC reports that iPad is the highest-scoring product the American Consumer Satisfaction Index (ACSI) has ever tracked.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 11:21:39 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>iPod touch is “the greatest iPod to date”</title>
<link>http://gear.ign.com/articles/111/1119491p1.html</link>
<description>IGN calls iPod touch “the greatest iPod to date,” noting its new A4 processor, built-in cameras, FaceTime video calling, and Retina display — which results in “incredibly smooth and detailed menus, game graphics, photos, and video playback.” The reviewer adds that the hardware improvements make iPod touch “uniquely prepared to take on richer, more complex games” and that “the latest model may be a worthy upgrade for gaming applications alone.”</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 17:19:15 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>iPod nano All About Music</title>
<link>http://techland.com/2010/09/13/apple-ipod-nano-2010-review-better-than-expected/ </link>
<description>Reviewing iPod nano, Peter Ha (TIME.com) writes that “the current generation nano is focused on one thing and one thing only — music.” Citing its small size, extremely responsive Multi-Touch display, and “intuitive UI,” Ha notes that iPod nano “now rivals the shuffle as the smallest iPod and the touch as one of the coolest and ‘funnest’ iPods ever made.”</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 17:14:02 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>iPad in Business Profiles</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/ipad/business/profiles/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>From world-class hospitality to medical rehabilitation, iPad is helping to transform the way businesses work. See how Hyatt Hotels &amp; Resorts, RehabCare, and other organizations are using iPad to improve the way they get business done.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 17:42:11 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Increasing Student Achievement with Mac</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/education/stories/greene-county/#video-greene-county?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Watch this video profile to see how the Mac has changed the way teachers teach and students learn in the Greene County school system in rural North Carolina. A new project-based curriculum has engaged and motivated students, and college-going rates have risen dramatically.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 17:40:25 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ping Users Top One Million in First 48 Hours</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/itunes/ping/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today announced that in less than 48 hours since its launch on Wednesday, more than one million users have joined Ping, its new social network for music. Ping lets users follow their favorite artists and friends to discover what music they’re talking about, listening to, and downloading. “One-third of the people who have downloaded iTunes 10 have joined Ping,“ said Eddy Cue, Apple’s vice president of Internet Services. “As many more people download iTunes 10 in the coming weeks, we expect the Ping community to continue growing.“</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 18:29:13 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>iMac Is “the ultimate all-in-one”</title>
<link>http://www.computerworld.com/s/article/9182725/Apple_s_27_in._iMac_the_center_of_my_digital_universe_</link>
<description>Computerworld reviewer Michael deAgonia writes that for “the past month, the latest 27-inch iMac from Apple has been the center of my digital universe.” Citing the computer’s high-resolution LED-backlit display, clean design, and speed, deAgonia concludes: “The iMac is pretty much everything I could want from a modern computer, the ultimate all-in-one.”</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 18:20:44 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>New Bento 3 Project Manager</title>
<link>http://www.filemaker.com/bpmhotnews</link>
<description>FileMaker, Inc. announced the Bento 3 Project Manager, a brand new set of templates designed to make it easy for Mac users to track their personal projects and manage their time within one integrated, intuitive place. The Bento 3 Project Manager includes a free 30-day trial of the popular Bento 3 personal database for Mac, plus two professionally designed, ready-to-use templates.</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2010 10:54:26 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Introduces New iPod touch, iPod nano, and iPod shuffle</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/ipod/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>The new iPod touch features Apple’s stunning Retina display, FaceTime video calling, HD video recording, A4 chip, 3-axis gyro, iOS 4.1, and Game Center — all combined in the thinnest and lightest iPod touch ever. The instantly wearable iPod nano, now completely redesigned with Multi-Touch, lets users navigate their music collections by simply tapping or swiping a finger on the display. And the colorful, clip-and-go iPod shuffle — with buttons, VoiceOver, and playlists — offers the very best features of iPod shuffle at only $49.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 12:34:36 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Introduces iTunes 10 with Ping</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/itunes/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>iTunes 10 features Ping, a new social network for music that lets you follow your favorite artists and friends to discover what music they’re talking about, listening to, and downloading. With Ping you can post your thoughts and opinions, your favorite albums and songs, and the music you’ve downloaded from iTunes — plus view concert listings and tell your friends which concerts you plan to attend.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 12:23:43 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Premieres New Apple TV</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/appletv/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>The new Apple TV offers the simplest way to watch your favorite HD movies and TV shows on your HD TV for the breakthrough price of just $99. With Apple TV, you can choose from the largest online selection of HD movies to rent, including first-run movies for just $4.99, and the largest online selection of HD TV show episodes to rent — from ABC, ABC Family, Fox, Disney Channel, and BBC America — for just 99 cents.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 12:21:05 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Mac Pro Is Go-To Choice for Creative Professionals</title>
<link>http://computershopper.com/desktops/reviews/apple-mac-pro-2010-version</link>
<description>Computer Shopper makes the quad-core Mac Pro an Editors’ Choice, citing its speedy performance, easy upgradability, and new lower price. The reviewers write: “Creative professionals who need a machine with both muscle and good looks, and Mac fans who love to game, will find a lot to like in the new Mac Pro.”</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 17:30:09 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>iTunes U Downloads Top 300 Million</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/education/why-apple/#itunes-u?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>In just over three years, iTunes U downloads have topped 300 million — making it one of the world’s most popular online educational catalogs. A dedicated area within the iTunes Store, iTunes U offers users public access to university courses, lab demonstrations, special lectures, and more from world class institutions such as Harvard, MIT, Cambridge, Oxford, University of Melbourne, and Université de Montréal.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 15:15:02 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Auto Innovators Roll with iPhone and Custom Apps</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/iphone/business/profiles/jm-family/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>JM Family — an $8 billion diversified automotive company and the largest Toyota distributor on the planet — has integrated iPhone and business apps available in the App Store into all of their daily operations. The company has also created a custom app that enables their sales organization to quickly track, review, and update dealership numbers.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2010 12:30:12 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple iAd Partners Happy with Early Results</title>
<link>http://latimesblogs.latimes.com/technology/2010/08/apple-ad-partners-happy-with-early-iad-results.html</link>
<description>The Los Angeles Times reports that Apple’s iAd mobile advertising platform is “getting favorable reviews from the companies whose advertisements were the first to run on the new system.” The article quotes Joe Jacoby, a senior manager of Nissan’s media operations, who says, “What iAd promises is the most progressive thing I’ve seen to date” in digital advertising.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2010 11:35:19 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sophisticated But Simple iMac</title>
<link>http://www.pcmag.com/print_article2/0,1217,a=253557,00.asp?hidPrint=true</link>
<description>PC Magazine makes the new quad-core 27-inch iMac an Editors’ Choice, calling it “a highly sophisticated, yet simple to use media PC.” The magazine found the new iMac to be faster than other all-in-one models they’ve recently tested and concludes that it “cements the Apple iMac as the all-in-one desktop to have and to beat.”</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2010 11:35:00 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Eat Pray Love Goes From Page to Screen via Final Cut Pro</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/finalcutstudio/in-action/eatpraylove/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Editor Bradley Buecker describes how he cut his first feature film, Eat Pray Love, using Final Cut Pro. To edit more than 70 hours of footage shot on location in New York, Italy, India, and Indonesia, Buecker found a fast, efficient editing format in ProRes 422 (Proxy), introduced in Final Cut Pro 7.</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 12:21:52 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>iPad Opens Up New Worlds for Autistic Children</title>
<link>http://www.sfweekly.com/2010-08-11/news/ihelp-for-autism/</link>
<description>SF Weekly profiles a Redwood City mother, Shannon Rosa, who blogged that iPad had helped her nine-year-old autistic son, Leo. “With the iPad, Leo electrifies the air around him with independence and daily new skills,” she wrote. The article credits Rosa’s post with contributing to a “quiet revolution” in the autistic community focused on using iPad for teaching communication and social skills to autistic children.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 12:30:48 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>